[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From what film is this dialog taken?  I do wish we could chat longer, but.....Im having an old friend for dinner. Bye", "correct_answer": "The Silence of the Lambs", "incorrect_answers": ["The Red Dragon", "Hannibal", "Seven"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which film can you hear this chilling quote in?\nHuman beings are a disease, a cancer of this planet. You are a plague, and we are the cure.", "correct_answer": "The Matrix", "incorrect_answers": ["Plan 9 from Outer Space", "Virus", "Mars Attacks!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cinnamon is believed to have a beneficial effect in the treatment of which of the following conditions?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Diarrhea", "Diabetes", "Common cold"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which pop legend featured zombies in the video for his song Thriller?", "correct_answer": "Michael Jackson", "incorrect_answers": ["Bruce Springsteen", "Phil Collins", "Justin Timberlake"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the first singer to have two singles that sold over 30 million copies worldwide?", "correct_answer": "Bing Crosby", "incorrect_answers": ["Bruce Springsteen", "Yanni", "Elton John"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish this Irish saying: Often has the likely failed and the unlikely _________.", "correct_answer": "succeeded", "incorrect_answers": ["failed too", "wrote a novel about the failure", "laughed at the failure"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In AFIs list of movies, the Top Ten were all made from the 1930s to the 1990s, however no film on the Top Ten list was made in the 1980s.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the role of Draco Malfoy in the Harry Potter film series?", "correct_answer": "Tom Felton", "incorrect_answers": ["Daniel Radcliffe", "Rupert Grint", "Richard Harris"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why were Thylacines called Tigers?", "correct_answer": "because of the stripes on their back", "incorrect_answers": ["because of the vicious way in which they killed their prey", "because they looked like cats", "because of their mean disposition"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "She was called The Swedish Nightingale.", "correct_answer": "Jenny Lind", "incorrect_answers": ["Ingrid Bergmann", "Bjork", "Agnetha Faltskog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does the name Kansas come from?", "correct_answer": "from the indigenous people of that area of the USA", "incorrect_answers": ["from the Chinook word for the area", "from an Apache word meaning small rivers", "from a Huron word meaning long space"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of the movie Planes, Trains  Automobiles, the the two main characters go to the bus station in Chicago and then go separate ways.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]